Happy, angry, amazed - these are some of the emotions we like to express these days when we‘re sending a message on our smartphones!
开心、生气、惊讶——这些是我们如今在智能手机上发消息时喜欢表达的一些情绪！
That’s why many of us now add little pictures to our texts to brighten up someone‘s mobile screen but we’re also using them as a quick way of telling someone how we‘re feeling.
这就是为什么我们很多人现在会在信息中添加小图片来点亮别人的手机屏幕，而且我们也把它们当作一种快速告诉别人我们感受的方式。
Yes, emojis have become a vital tool for communication.
没错，表情符号已经成为了一种重要的交流工具。
Let’s clear one thing up first - there are emojis and emoticons.
我们首先要弄清楚一件事——有表情符号（emojis）和表情符号（由键盘字符组成的）（emoticons）。
The latter are little images made using normal keys on a keyboard.
后者是用键盘上的普通按键组成的小图像。
For example, a colon, two dots, followed by the curved line of a close brackets is a ‘smiley face‘.
例如，一个冒号（:），两个点，再加上右括号的曲线（）组成一个“笑脸”。
But as technology has become more sophisticated, pre-made images have been created that can be simply added to your messages, which is great!
但是随着技术变得越来越复杂精密，预先制作好的图像可以被简单地添加到你的消息中，这太棒了！
The emoji was first invented in Japan in the late 1990s and the word ’emoji‘ comes from the Japanese words for ’picture‘ and ’character‘.
表情符号最早是在20世纪90年代末在日本发明的，“emoji”这个词来自日语中表示“图片”和“字符”的词。
The number of different images has dramatically increased since then and now we have a picture for every mood or situation.
从那以后，图像的数量大幅地增加了，现在我们每种情绪或情况都有对应的图片。
So now we have the option to give this new creation the visual ’thumbs-up‘ but have you thought (puzzled face) why we’ve become so addicted to using emojis?
所以现在我们可以选择给这个新事物一个视觉上的“点赞”，但是你有没有想过（疑惑的表情）为什么我们会如此沉迷于使用表情符号呢？
Professor Vyv Evans, has written a book called ‘The Emoji Code‘ - he says “increasingly, what we‘re finding is that digital communication is taking over from certain aspects of face-to-face interaction... one of the reasons emojis are so interesting is that they really do enable us to express our emotional selves much more effectively.”
维夫·埃文斯教授写了一本名为《表情符号密码》的书——他说：“我们发现，数字交流正在逐渐越来越多地取代某些面对面的交流……表情符号如此有趣的原因之一是，它们确实能让我们更有效地表达我们的情绪。”
So emojis are a sort of substitute for the visual signals or non-verbal cues we normally give when we speak to someone face-to-face.
所以表情符号是我们在面对面和别人交谈时通常给出的视觉信号或非语言暗示的一种替代品。
Another advantage of emojis is that they are an international language - they don‘t use words but tell a message in pictorial form so they can be easily interpreted whatever your native language.
表情符号的另一个优点是它们是一种国际语言——它们不使用文字，而是以图画的形式传达信息，所以无论你的母语是什么，它们都很容易被理解。
However, the emojis you send need some thought as they can sometimes be misinterpreted - if a friend sends you an emoji of a hammer, you may think he is angry when really he is saying he has hurt himself or he is clumsy!
然而，你发送的表情符号需要斟酌，因为它们有时可能会被误解——如果一个朋友给你发送一个锤子的表情符号，你可能会认为他生气了，而实际上他是说他弄伤了自己或者他很笨拙！
Emojis are a good way for showing empathy - they are a virtual hug or a flirtatious tease.
表情符号是表达共情的好方法——它们就像一个虚拟的拥抱或者一个轻浮的挑逗。
But as linguist Neil Cohn says, “to many, emoji are an exciting evolution of the way we communicate; to others, they are linguistic Armageddon.”
但是正如语言学家尼尔·科恩所说：“对很多人来说，表情符号是我们交流方式的一次令人兴奋的进化；对另一些人来说，它们是语言的大灾难。”
It does show there is a lot more to our communication than words alone but does this mean the decline in traditional writing?
这确实表明我们的交流不仅仅是文字，但这是否同时也意味着传统写作的衰落呢？